Narisara Sangbunluerit

09-44802543 · narisara.sangbunluerit@gmail.com Samut Prakan, Thailand

UX/UI DESIGNER

I graduated from Computer Science at KMITL. I'm writing to apply for working. I specialize in UX/UI design almost 1 year. I'm creating projects according to the Design Thinking process for solving a problem. I'm currently interested in UX/UI Designer and looking forward to experiencing new things to upskill myself. I believe that my dedication to my field makes me become a useful member of your company. I'm excited to be a part of the team. Thank you for considering my application.

SKILLS

UX/UI Design

- Design Thinking Process
- User Research, Stakeholder Interviews, Online Survey, Questionnaire, Contextual Inquiry, Interview, Observation
- Persona, User Journey Map, User Scenario, User Flow Diagram, Hierarchical Task Analysis, Empathy Map, Storyboard, Comparative Analysis
- Information Architecture, Interaction Design, Visual Interface Design, UX Writing, Pixel Perfect
- Wireframe(low-fidelity), Mockup(High-fidelity), Prototype, Design system
- Usability Testing, Cognitive Walkthrough, Heuristic Evaluation, Guerrilla Testing, Remote Testing, System Usability Scale

Tools & Programming

- Figma, Adobe XD
- CSS, HTML, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, React
- Maze, Useberry
- Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator
- · Canva, FigJam, Lucid chart
- Jira, Trello

Soft Skills

- Interpersonal, collaborative, and communication
- Problem-Solving
- Prioritization and time management
- Understanding of Design Principles
- Empathy
- Curiosity and continuous learning

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE (1)

EdVISORY CO., LTD. 2023 - Present

Junior UX/UI Design (Contract 6 months)

Design the company's products and projects based on user experience. That helps Reduce time and steps from job opening to screening. Until onboarding allows the organization to get more people who meet its needs.

EdVISORY CO., LTD. 2023 - 2023

UX/UI Design (Internship 3 months)

Design a website to learn tools in Figma and the Design process. I create design projects to use for promoting the company's products to be more interesting

SPECIAL PROBLEM 1 2023 - 2023

UX/UI Design (Graduation project)

Web application of the Faculty of Science KMITL and The Central System for Computer Science design for departments of the KMITL website, Support Responsive Design and SEO, using Design Thinking.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE (2)

SPECIAL PROBLEM 1 2023 - 2023

UX/UI Design (Graduation project)

Web application of the Faculty of Science KMITL (Redesign) by using User interface design for development in all departments of the KMITL web application based on user experience to support Responsive Web Design and SEO using the Design Thinking process.

SPECIAL PROBLEM 1 2023

UX/UI Design (Graduation project)

The central system for students of the Department of Computer Science which Designed a central system that can support all microservices used by computer science students. I was using the Design Thinking process.

DESIGNING INTERACTIVE SYSTEMS

2022

UX/UI Design (project)

Design an application for drug delivery from hospitals. To reduce the chance of contracting COVID-19 and using User Research.

HUMAN-COMPUTER INTERACTION

2021

UX/UI Design (project)

Web application design for an e-commerce website to learn to use the different tools in Figma.

EDUCATION

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang

Bachelor of Science Program in Computer Science (2019 - 2023) GPA 3.55

Saint Joseph Thiphawan School

Sciences and Mathematics Program (2013 - 2019) GPA 3.98